Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores, 1930-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Compilations and sketchbooks, 1935-2004, III; Folder 229-427
  - Gearhart, Livingston Sax sessions [between 1984 and 1988], 1 box (52 folders).; Materials are for Sax Sessions, a proposed addition to the Sessions series published by Shawnee Press which was never published. For various combinations of saxophones. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on 
    Contents: Sax session correspondence and documents -- 1. A bad egg -- 2. Canon ("Hindemith") -- 6. Dziekuje / Brubeck -- 7. From the Strenuous life / Joplin -- 8. Allegro bellicoso / Scriabin -- 9. Calcutta blues / Brubeck -- 10. Danke Schön / Brubeck -- 11. Golden horn / Brubeck -- 12. Greeting to "G" / Schumann -- 13. Madrigal / Palestrina -- 14. Ostinato (?) / Brubeck -- 15. Santa lucia -- 16. La Verginella / Andrea Gabrieli -- 17. [We wish you a merry Christmas: for chorus and orchestra] -- 18. Alle Menschen Müssen Sterben / J.S. Bach -- 19. Auld lang syne -- 20. Base, vile blues -- 21. (From) Come, Holy Ghost / Thomas Attwood -- 22 Count me out / J. Lunceford -- 23. David's lamentation / William Billings -- 24. Equali 1 / Ludwig van Beethoven -- 25. Fire-bird themes / Stravinsky -- 27. Fugue / Haydn -- 28. Gagliarda del Principe di Venosa / Carlo Gesualdo -- 29. Habanera -- 30. Les langueurs tendres / C.P.E. Bach -- 31. Antiques refinished: Marche / Johann Fischer -- 32. Prayer / César Franck -- 33. Russian dance -- 34. Sinfonia IX / J.S. Bach -- 35. Forlane: for 4 saxophones; Sicilenne: for 4 flutes -- 36. Rondo / Ignaz Pleyel -- 37. Sonate für zwei Querflöten oder zwei Violinen, D-dur / Georg Philipp Telemann -- 38. Andante from Sonata, op. 26 / Ludwig van Beethoven -- 39. Fanfare / Traditional -- 41. Hopak / Modest Mussorgsky -- 42. Petit(?)e fanfare: for 4 flutes -- 43. Andante religioso, op. 65 / Felix Mendelssohn -- 44. March and hornpipe -- 45. Marble arch / Brubeck -- 46. [Untitled piece] / F. Nietzsche -- 47. Procession of the nobles / Rimsky-Korsakov -- 49. Colloquoy -- 50. [Untitled piece] / C.P.E. Bach -- 51. Art of fugue (Fragment) / J.S. Bach -- 52. Air / J.S. Bach -- 53. Hunting song / Johannes Brahms -- 54. Kloster Fraülein: op. 69 / Schumann -- 55. [Untitled piece] / Haydn -- 56. [Untitled canon] / Giovanni Matteo Asola -- 57. Duo / Leopold Mozart.
  - A singing bee: two-part songs for treble voices, S.A., with descants and optional divisi 1956, 1 score (96 p.); 27 cm.; Edited by Lara Hoggard. On cover: The Fred Waring Music Workshop. Forty-nine familiar and new songs, with piano accompaniment for intermediate and junior high grades. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 21, Folder 420)
    Contents: America-our heritage -- Michael Finnigin -- This is my Father's world -- Some folks -- Sometimes I feel like a motherless child -- Grandfather's clock -- Little Joe, the wrangler -- Katie the kangaroo -- My shadow -- Christ the Lord is risen today -- Prayer -- Cindy -- The Marine's hymn -- The crazy song -- Good news! -- The tempo song -- I love school -- A futile serenade (Pancho's plight) -- I got shoes -- Stars of the summer night -- Goober peas -- This is my country -- Limerick parade (The enunciator's nightmare) -- Come, ye thankful people, come -- Musical clocks -- Dr. Eisenbart -- Musical mirror -- Wandering -- Vive l'amour -- Big Rock Candy Mountain -- Git along, little dogies -- When Johnny comes marching home -- Vesper hymn -- Big Chief Wotapotami -- Polly Wolly Doodle -- Who did? -- Onward Christian soldiers -- O how lovely is the evening -- Brahms' lullaby -- Don't slip -- The caissons song -- Joy to the world! -- The Christ Child -- Away in a manger -- I heard the bells on Christmas day -- We three kings -- What child is this? -- Morning prayer -- Evening prayer.
  - String mix 1976, 1 score (32 p.) + 7 parts; 28 cm.; For youth orchestra. Cover title. Biographical note about Livingston Gearhart precedes score. Publisher's no. stamped on cover. LC lacks score. DLC Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 21, Folder 421)
    Contents: Carol of the bells / Leontovich -- In dulci jubilo / J. S. Bach -- Pavane / Schreiber -- Sand mountain blues -- Echo / Notsgnivil -- Il est ne? --Andante religioso / Mendelssohn -- Chorale -- Sinfonica economica / after Haydn -- Hark! the herald angels sing / Mendelssohn -- Canon over a ground bass / Purcell.
  - String mix. 1976, 1 miniature score (32 p.); 18 cm.; Cover title. For youth orchestra. Note about the music precedes score; postscript biographical note about Livingston Gearhart. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - Gearhart, Livingston Treble clef sessions [between 1990 and 1996], 1 ms. score ([25] leaves); 30 x 38 cm.; Alternate title: Rhythm book. Contains complete ms. for Treble clef sessions published by Shawnee Press in 2000. Title supplied by cataloger. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 21, Folder 423)
    Contents: 2.0. Utter simplicity -- 3.0. Beethoven themes I and II -- 3.1. As fast as you can -- 3.3. Suspensions I -- 3.4. Suspensions II -- Variations on a theme from Petrouchka -- The significance of [quarter rest] -- 4.0LR. Inward counting (Two duos) -- 4.1 La campanella / Paganini -- 4.2. Bulgarian melody -- 4.0LR. Inward counting -- 4.3. Mixed metre -- 4.4. Vulgarian music -- 4.5. Andante doloroso -- 4.6. Canon in two speeds -- 4.7 Jazz (Sort of) -- 4.8. Count two (Think four) -- 5.0. Like, Ping pong: Three canons. Volley for serve; 5.1. Backhand; 5.2. Trick shot -- 5.3LR. Interiorization -- V4. Scherzo theme / Beethoven -- Three different ways of writing the same music -- Interiorization -- V5. Any kind of note can get one beat -- V6. Step-by-step progression -- 5.5. We gather -- 5.6. Valse triste -- 5.7. Broadway hit of 1910 / Romberg -- 5.8. Melody / Schubert -- 5.9. Waltz / Brahms -- 6.0. Il botcho / Arditi -- 6.1. From Artist's life -- 6.11 O Logie O'Buchan / Scotch -- 6.12 The unconstant lover (...Is worse than any thief) / Appalachia -- 6.2. Syncopation explication in two movements -- 6.21 Bethena: Ragtime waltz / Joplin -- 6.3. Familiar? -- 6.4. More syncopation in 3 steps -- 6.41. Jazz-related figures -- 7.0. Not a waltz / Grieg -- 7.1. An teicead so heisipt: Flight into Egypt / Irish -- 7.2. Air / Purcell -- 7.3. Unfinished business / Schubert -- 7.4. Kastchei's infernal dance (Theme) / Stravinsky -- 7.5. Rosetta stone I -- 7.6. Rosetta stone II -- Careful!: in three movements -- 8.1. Lament canon at one bar -- 8.2. A displaced rhythm -- 8.3. Sinfonia Brevis -- 8.31. Something hidden -- 9.0. Pavane theme / Ravel -- 9.1. In the garden / Russian -- 9.2. Slightly distorted (Achtung!): [two versions] -- 10.0 [Published as Challenge I (How many steps can you skip?)] -- 10.1. Two-note tango -- 10.2. Okay, 3 notes -- 10.3. [Published as Challenge II] -- 10.4. Two-note tango -- 10.5. Okay, three notes -- 11.0. Important comparison -- 11.1. Comin' through the rye / Scotch -- 11.2. Comin' through the rye -- 11.3. Erie canal excavated / U.S. -- 11.4. Suez canal -- 11.5. [Untitled] -- 11.6. [Untitled] -- 11.7. Finnegan's wake (He awoke at his wake) -- 11.8. Finnegan's wake -- 12.0 Hopak / Mussorgsky -- 12.1. Putative Amerindian tuned: used by Dvorak -- 12.2. Concerto theme / Handel -- 12.3. Etude / Leopold Mozart -- 12.4. Hornpipe / Brit. -- 12.5. Rough stuff I -- 12.6. Rough stuff II -- 12.7. Chaik II -- 12.8. [Untitled] -- 13.0. Fanfare figure / Verdi -- 13.1. If you have it--reinforce it: [from Tchaikovsky's Fifth symphony] -- 13.2. How come the double dot? (It saves energy) -- 13.3. [Untitled] -- 13.5. Symphony fragment / Wm. Herschel -- 14.0. Sudden action -- 14.1. The interpolator -- 14.2. Calm after the storm / Musorgskii -- 14.3. [Untitled] -- 14.4. [Untitled] / Haydn -- 14.5. The world's longest wait / Chaikovsky -- 15.0. Fussy composers clutter the page. A framework; Embellished; How Haydn wrote it; 15.1. He wanted to stress the idea of separation, as Dvorak did in; 15.2 or, as Chaikovsky did, in; 15.3 But, watch out for this one / Prokofiev; 15.4. [Untitled] -- 16.0. Easing into Ragtime -- 16.1. Exercise no. 5 (from School of ragtime, Joplin, 1908) -- 16.2. The entertainer / Joplin -- 16.3. Golliwog theme / Debussy -- 16.4. The "occasional triplet" -- 16.6. What's the difference? -- 16.7. Tune from a march / Meyerbeer -- 16.5. Polka rhythm -- 16.8. 6/8: a pair of threes -- 17.0. A most minimal melody (With increasingly vexatious accompaniment patterns) / Offenbach -- 17.1. Tema Espagnole / Lalo -- 17.2. Llwyn on / Welsh -- 17.3. Think six -- 17.4. Think two -- 17.5. Collisions / J.S. Bach -- 17.6. Challenge -- 17.7. "Skelsss" (Scales with a Russian Accent) -- 17.8. The basic model -- 17.9. "Spanish" / Rimski-Korsakoff -- 18.0. [Untitled] / Rimski-K. -- 19.1. [Untitled] / R. Strauss -- 18.2. [Untitled] / Half-Bach -- 18.3. Mixed metre -- 19.4. [Untitled] -- 18.5. [Untitled] -- 18.6. [Untitled] -- 19.0. Slow is hard. Wintertime / Schumann; 19.1. Also (Niemals) Sprach Zarathustra / F. Nietzsche; 19.2. Late Brahms; 19.3. Late Bach; 19.4. Polonaise / Chopin; 19.5. Polonaise / J.S. B[ach] -- 20.0. Music of Athens (Georgia, that is) -- 20.1. Motet (Music of the church) / Giovanni Matteo Asola -- 20.3. Veni Emmanuel -- 20.4. Brobdingnagian jig.
  - Treble clef sessions: a collection of duets for [treble clef] instruments guaranteed to sharpen and enhance rhythm skills and sight reading 2000, 1 score (71 p.); 31 cm.; Biographical note about Livingston Gearhart precedes score. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 21, Folder 424)
    Contents: Legend -- Utter simplicity -- Beethoven themes I and II -- Suspensions I and II -- Variations on a theme from Petrouchka -- Inward counting (Two duos) -- The significance of [quarter rest] -- La campanella -- Inward counting (Two duos) -- Bulgarian melody -- Mixed metre -- Vulgarian music -- Andante doloroso -- Canon in two speeds -- Jazz (Sort of) -- Count two (Think four) -- Like, Ping pong: Three canons. Volley for serve; Backhand; Trick shot -- Interiorization -- Scherzo theme -- Three different ways of writing the same music -- Interiorization -- Any kind of note can get one beat -- Step-by-step progression -- We gather -- Valse triste -- Broadway hit of 1910 -- Melody -- Waltz -- Il botcho (Bacio) -- O Logie O'Buchan -- From Artist's life -- The unconstant lover (...Is worse than any thief) -- Syncopation explication in two steps -- Bethena Ragtime waltz -- Familiar? -- More syncopation in three steps -- Jazz-related figures -- Not a waltz -- An teicead so heisipt: Flight into Egypt -- Air -- Unfinished business -- Katschei's infernal dance (Theme) -- Careful!: in three movements -- Lament canon at one bar -- Rosetta stone I -- Rosetta stone II -- Sinfonia Brevis -- A displaced rhythm -- Something hidden -- Pavane theme -- In the garden -- Slightly distorted (Achtung!): two versions -- Bottom of the ninth -- Double-play at (the) third (from an early book on How to compose) -- Not the way they sing it -- Challenge I (How many steps can you skip?) -- Two-note tango -- Challenge II -- Two-note tango -- Okay, three notes -- Important comparison (Metronome markings) -- Okay, three notes -- Comin' through the rye -- Comin' through the rye -- Erie canal excavated -- Suez canal -- Melody -- Increasingly hazardous -- Increasingly hazardous -- Finnegan's wake (He awoke at his wake) -- Putative Amerindian tune -- Finnegan's wake -- Hornpipe -- Hopak -- Concerto theme -- Etude -- Eternal vigilance -- Rough stuff I -- Rough stuff II -- Chaik II -- Gotcha I -- Symphony fragment -- Fanfare figure -- If you have it--reinforce it -- Sudden action -- The interpolator -- Sudden action -- Conversazione -- Interjacence -- Calm after the storm -- The world's longest wait -- How come the double dot (It saves energy and ink) -- Fussy composers clutter the page. A framework; Embellished; How Haydn wrote it -- Easing into Ragtime -- Exercise no. 5 (from School of ragtime, Joplin, 1908) -- The entertainer -- Golliwog theme -- The "occasional triplet" -- What's the difference? -- Polka rhythm -- Tune from a march -- 6/8: a pair of threes -- A most minimal melody (With increasingly vexatious accompaniment patterns) -- Tema Espagnole -- Llwyn on -- Think six -- Think two -- Collision -- Challenge III (Visualize the dot) -- "Skelsss" (Scales with a Russian Accent) -- The basic model -- Scheherazade -- "Spanish" -- Name this tune -- Half-Bach -- Mixed metre -- Gotcha II -- Take turns -- Prep for Brahms -- Slow is hard. Wintertime; Also (Niemals) Sprach Zarathustra; Late Brahms; Late Bach; Polonaise; Polonaise -- Motet (Music of the church) -- Music of Athens (Georgia, that is!) -- Veni Emmanuel -- Brobdingnagian jig -- Fragment: Le sacre du printemps (Final dance).
  - Gearhart, Livingston Trick pieces: rounds and canons [between 1970 and 1996?], 1 folder.; For various unspecified instrumentations. Title from accompanying leaf. Holograph (Pencil and ink). Accompanied by 2 typescript notes; 10 typewritten and handwritten index cards by Livingston Gearhart. (Box 21, Folder 425)
    Contents: Democracy: four-part round -- Table music -- Scherzo -- Season's greetings -- Gavotte in the Dorian mode -- [Untitled piece -- Ho capito: from] Don Giovanni / Mozart -- Sinfonia economica -- On one note -- [Untitled piece] -- Round for three players / Beethoven -- Tick-tock caper (?): 3 part round.
  - Trumpet sessions 1950, 1 score (56 p.); 31 cm.; "For two, three and four trumpets unaccompanied. For intermediate and advanced players. A variety of styles from Palestrina to jazz ... All the music in this collection is playable on both clarinets and violins." Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 21, Folder 426)
    Contents: Allegro / Mozart -- Aria / Weber -- The bells of St. Vitus (Canon) / Arranged -- Bonnie's bounce / Lessac -- Boogie in canon / Arranged -- Bugle woogie (Round) / Devinez -- Canon / Drissecoeur -- Chili con corni / Castiglioni -- Chinese lullaby (Canon) / Based on a Chinese folk song -- Chorale / Wagner -- Chromatic study / Neinstein -- Count me in (Round) / Caldara -- Count me out / Lunceford -- Ditto / Arranged -- Duettino / C.P.E. Bach -- Equali no. 2 / Beethoven -- Esercizio sopra la scala / Palestrina -- Fanfare for a ballerina / Stravinsky -- Fanfare for a celebration / de Falla -- Fanfare for a king / des Pres -- Fanfare for a pompous circumstance / Bax -- Fanfare for a procession / Debussy -- Fanfare for twenty trumpets / Weber -- Fanfare for a victory / Verdi -- Fanfare for a wolf / Prokofieff -- Fanfare from hunger / Traditional -- Fanfare "Pour le roi des singes" / Satie -- Five by five (Canon) / Quintus V -- Flourish for trumpets / Leopold Mozart -- Frankenstein's revenge / Neinstein -- Gloria / J.S. Bach -- Hare and tortoise / Joe Aesop -- Hark the herald angels sing / Mendelssohn -- Hunting song / Brahms -- Inside the atom bomb / Neinstein -- Jazz on rye / Chateau -- Jericho (Canon) / Gerard -- Jingle bells / Santa Claus -- Lacrimosa / Schubert -- Lament / Brahms -- March for trumpets / Handel -- March funebre (Canon) / Steibelt -- Minuet / J.S. Bach -- MinueTeuniM / Al Rovescio -- Nocturne / Mendelssohn -- Pavane (Theme) / Ravel -- Polka (Canon) / Malácek -- Presto (Round) / Haydn -- Prima gagliarda / Zozzi -- Round / Purcell -- Riffn' around / Arranged -- Russian dance / Updownsky -- Sarabande / Anon. 17th century -- Strange interlude / Neinstein -- Trepak / After Tschaikovsky, etc. -- Trio / C.P.E. Bach -- Trumpet bells / Arranged -- Variations on a theme of Paganini / Stolen from Brahms -- Volga boatmen / Untraditional.
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Quintets, violins, violas, violoncello, K. 614, E♭ major; arranged Quintett: 2 pianos [between 1935 and 1950], 1 ms. sketchbook ([46] p.); 35 cm.; Includes "two pages of what seem to be 'exercises,' probably while studying with Scalero at Curtis"--Accompanying leaf. According to Gearhart's note, the Mozart Quintet arranged for 2 pianos was arranged by Robert Casadesus, written in the hand of Virginia Morley [Waring]. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil and ink). Includes 1 photocopied letter from Livingston Gearhart to Carol Bradley (1 leaf) with Gearhart's description of the contents. (Box 21, Folder 427)
- Annotated scores, 1930-1960, IV; Folder 428-507; The range of dates for the series indicates the likely period during which the scores were annotated, not the publication dates.
  - Arensky, Anton Stepanovich, 1861-1906 Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 15. Suite for Two Pianos, Op. 15 1930-1960, 1 part; Publisher: A. Gutheil Title page missing Piano II part only. Score contains few performance annotations in pencil. (Box 22, Folder 428)
  - Arensky, Anton Stepanovich, 1861-1906 Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 15 Suite for Two Pianos, Op. 15. Edited and fingered by Louis Oesterle 1930-1960, 2 parts; Publisher: G. Schirmer Piano 1 part contains moderate performance annotations in pencil and blue pencil (fingerings and phrase markings). Piano 2 part contains few performance annotations in pencil. (Box 22, Folder 429)
  - Arensky, Anton Stepanovich, 1861-1906 Suites, pianos (2), no. 1, op. 15. Valse Suite for Two Pianos, Op. 15, no. 2. Valse. Edited and fingered by Louis Oesterle 1930-1960, 1 part; Publisher: [G. Schirmer] Incomplete: Includes only p.3-9. Piano II part only (incomplete). Score contains few annotations for performance in pencil and blue pencil (fingerings only). (Box 22, Folder 430)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Brandenburgische Konzerte. Nr. 5; arranged Tripel-Konzert Nr. 2. Für Klavier, Violine und Flöte mit Begleitung, D. Bearbeitung von C. Krug 1930-1960, 2 parts; Publisher: Breitkopf and Härtel Originally for chamber orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. The piece is Brandenburg concerto no. 5 by J.S. Bach. Parts heavily annotated for performance (with fingerings, dynamics, and phrasing markings). (Box 22, Folder 431)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Concertos, harpsichord, string orchestra, BWV 1052, D minor; arranged Concert in D Moll für Klavier und Streichorchester. Die Orchesterbegleitung für ein zweites Klavier bearbeitet von Julius Röntgen 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Universal Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Contains few annotations (rehearsal letters and phrase markings). (Box 22, Folder 432)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Concertos, harpsichords (2), string orchestra, BWV 1061, C major; arranged Konzert C dur für Zwei Klaviere. Herausgegeben von F. C. Griepenkerl 1930-1960, 2 two-piano scores; Publisher: C. F. Peters Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Piano 1 part contains annotations for performance (fingerings and phrase markings). Piano 2 part contains no annotations. (Box 22, Folder 433)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Concertos, harpsichords (3), string orchestra, BWV 1063, D minor Concerto for 3 Pianos in D Minor (B. W. 22) 1930-1960, 3 parts; Publisher: Reprint of Breitkopf and Härtel by Associated Music Publishers For 3 pianos and string orchestra. Piano 1 (2 copies), Piano 2 (1 copy) Parts annotated for performance in pencil and red pencil. (Box 22, Folder 434)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Concertos, harpsichords (3), string orchestra, BWV 1064, C major Concerto for 3 Pianos in C Major (B. W. 23) 1930-1960, 3 parts; Publisher: Reprint of Breitkopf and Härtel by Associated Music Publishers For 3 pianos and string orchestra. All covers of parts signed by Livingston Gearhart. Parts heavily annotated for performance (fingerings and phrase markings) in pencil and red pencil. (Box 22, Folder 435)
    Accompanied by [2] leaves of ms. Music copied in the hand of Livingston Gearhart.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Herz und Mund und Tat und Leben, BWV 147. Jesus bleibet meine Freude; arranged Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring. (Chorale from Cantata No. 147) / J.S. Bach. Arranged...by Myra Hess 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Oxford Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Score contains few annotations for performance in pencil. (Box 22, Folder 436)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Herz und Mund und Tat und Leben, BWV 147. Jesus bleibet meine Freude; arranged Chorale from Bach Cantata no. 147. Arranged for two pianos by Elsie Horne 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Murdoch Score contains no annotations. (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Jagdkantate. Schafe können sicher weiden; arranged Schafe Können sicher Weiden (Sheep May Safely Graze). Transcribed for two pianos by Mary Howe 1930-1960, 2 two-piano scores; Publisher: Oxford 1st piano score contains few performance annotations in pencil; 2nd score contains no annotations. (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Organ music. Selections Johann Sebastian Bach's Kompositionen für die Orgel. Kritisch-korrekte Ausgabe von Friedrich Conrad Griepenkerl und Ferdinand Roitzsch 1930-1960, 1 score each; Publisher: C. F. Peters For organ. Includes Bands I, III, IV, VI, VII, and IX; some are incomplete. Scores contain few performance annotations in pencil. Band I contains rehearsal letters and organ registrations; Band III contains phrase markings; Band IV contains one organ registration and few annotations; Band VI contains few phrase markings and organ registrations; Band VII contains moderate performance annotations (rehearsal letters, phrase markings, and organ registrations); Band IX contains few markings. (Box 22, Folder 439-444)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Präludium und Fuge, organ, BWV 532, D major; arranged Präludium und Fuge in D Dur. Übertragen von Otto Singer 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Steingraber Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Score contains few performance annotations in pencil. (Box 23, Folder 445)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Präludium und Fuge, organ, BWV 546, C minor; arranged Prelude and Fugue in C Minor. Arranged for two pianos by Harold Bauer 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Ditson Score contains moderate annotations for performance in pencil (fingerings, phrase markings, and dynamics). (Box 23, Folder 446)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Sonatas, flute, harpsichord, BWV 1031, E♭ major. Siciliano; arranged Sicilienne. Transcribed by Guy Maier 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: J. Fischer Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Score contains few annotations for performance in pencil (fingerings and phrase markings). (Box 23, Folder 447)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Toccatas, organ, BWV 565, D minor; arranged Toccata and Fugue in D Minor. Transcribed by Silvio Scionti 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: G. Ricordi Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Score contains few annotations for performance in pencil on p. 3 and 5 only. (Box 23, Folder 448)
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 Variationen über ein Thema des Grafen v. Waldstein; arranged Variations on a Theme by Count von Waldstein. Arranged for Two Pianos Four Hands by Victor Babin 1930-1960, 2 two-piano scores; Publisher: Elkan-Vogel Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Piano 1 score contains few annotations in pencil (fingerings); Piano 2 score contains no annotations. (Box 23, Folder 449)
  - Benjamin, Arthur, 1893-1960 Jamaican pieces. Jamaican rumba Jamaican Rhumba for Two Pianos-Four Hands 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Boosey and Hawkes Score contains few annotations in pencil on pp. 4-5 (fingerings). (Box 23, Folder 450)
  - Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897 Sonatas, pianos (2), op. 34b, F minor Sonate für zwei Pianoforte nach dem Quintett Op. 34 1930-1960, 1 two-piano score; Publisher: Breitkopf and Härtel Arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Part of title page missing Score contains moderate performance annotations in pencil (mainly fingerings and phrase markings). (Box 23, Folder 451)